No, I don't want to burn the internet down every day.
I was doing that for a while, though, because when people weren't gravitating towards me,
I was like, I know how to get y'all.
I know how to get everybody's attention.
I just started saying what I think in the most animated way, and yeah, it was very hurtful.
I don't feel bad about it.
That's just been a part of my journey.
I can still slip there.
Sometimes I still do, but I choose not to live in that every day.
I was in that every day.
Literally, I called my team.
Was that a reflection of where you were in your heart, like in your spirit?
It was that, and I was tired of the industry because there's a lot of in this industry.
Well, y'all know how I feel about this industry.